geofollow.com 2011-12-21

# DATEPRIVACY.doc

DATEFREE.MOBI PRIVACY POLICY

DateFree.mobi, and the owners and operators of DateFree.mobi, are committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy details how we use your personal identifying information. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice to you. Please review this document each time you visit us or use any of our tools or services.

We will never reveal your personal information to any third party or entity accept under the following circumstances:

•        If a governmental agency, or an attorney, subpoenas your private information, or makes a formal request for discovery pursuant to any legal action, or pending legal action. 

•        If our attorney requests such information relevant to a current or pending legal matter in which you are a potential or actual party or otherwise contributed in some way to the causation of the legal matter. 

Please note that we employ the use of “Cookies.”  Currently we employ “Cookies” when users create user accounts, but we may further employ “Cookies” to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future.

 “Cookies” are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we use “Cookies” to enhance your usage of our functions. 

As you employ our functions, your user name, password and email address is recorded in a DateFree.mobi database. A session “Cookie” is written to your browser for the purpose of maintaining an authenticated session with you, the user. 

The information gathered is not shared with third parties. You may turn off your “Cookies” by adjusting the appropriate setting on your browser. 

Please consult the HELP menu of your browser to learn how to turn your “Cookies” off. “Cookies” do not reveal personal information and if you turn off your “Cookies” you may find your enjoyment of the Internet, and our site, to be reduced or impaired. 

“Cookies” and IP addresses help us track visitors to our site and to the sites owned and maintained by our various customers. Providing such data to our customers is an inherent part of an important service we provide our contractees. 

Users who visit DateFree.mobi may have their IP address, user agent, and Internet based referrer automatically recorded in our log file. 

In order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use you email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes. 

We may also use you email and IP address to automatically recognize you should you contact us or use our tools and services. Groups of email and IP addresses are also gathered so that we may have broad demographic information. 

You may be required to complete online registration forms that provide us with contact information (such as your name and street address), your email address, and your phone numbers. 

We may, from time to time, send you emails regarding our service so that we can directly communicate with you regarding issues we determine to be relevant. We may also provide you with promotional information about our tools and services, as well as tools and services offered by our partners. An opt-out procedure is provided with each mailing regarding general offers or information. You must accept emails from us that deal with specific issues regarding your account or membership. This is because we may need to contact you if there is a change in the service that we are providing you or if we need to respond to an inquiry that you have sent us regarding a customer service issue or other important concern. 

Naturally, should you purchase a product or service from us, we will require sufficient information from you so that we can complete the transaction. Such information could include a credit card number and related account and billing data, invoice related information, and other data required for processing the order. We will also update such data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges, such as monthly or other types of periodic payments. All information of this nature is maintained by us in a secure database and transmitted across the Internet from you to us using secured transmission encryption. 

Please contact us if you should have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy. 

.
